[music]
Hey, welcome to another lunch and learn.
If this is the first time you're
joining, my name is Georgian Gaton. I am
the CEO and founder of GSC solutions and
I'm also an organizational systems
architect. What that means is simply I
build different systems and operations,
helping people connect technology,
operations, workflows, and how they be
more productive and get work done. So,
in today's episode, we're doing a little
something a little bit different. Let me
know what y'all think of the camera. So,
I'm using um my DJI Osmo Pocket 3 as a
webcam. So, I'm I'm kind of looking up
because the camera's up here, but the
screen is down here, and we're figuring
it out. But, this looks good. From what
I'm seeing, it looks really amazing. Um,
actually, when I'm looking at the
screen, it doesn't look too bad. So, you
let me know down below in the comments
what you think. If you're watching this
live, let's interact. Let's have a good
conversation. And if you're watching
this afterwards, let me know some
feedback in the uh comment section. But
in today's lunch and learn, what we're
going to be talking about is three ways
to maximize networking and events in the
age of AI. I know over the last few
years, me personally, I stopped going to
as many in-person events as I wanted to.
I wasn't doing as much networking. I
would connect with people on LinkedIn. I
would connect with people on social
media, but it wasn't as much interaction
as I actually actually wanted. And I'm
going to do something in real time with
y'all today right now because I didn't
know if this this setup is working. So,
I'm actually going to join.
>> All right. Audio is on. Everything is
working. I wanted to make sure the light
the LinkedIn is good. So now back into
it. Um what I was saying previously is
that with ver with everything going
digital and now with AI, it feels like
sometimes you don't really need to
network anymore or like there's so much
automation like why can't AI help you
out in that space? And I wanted to come
on and talk about the ways that I've
been using AI to maximize that my
networking and increase my network and
truly build valuable connections. So the
first thing I want to talk about is you
want to make sure that when you are
trying to network in the age of AI that
you know what you want to get out of the
event, the function, the connection, you
want to think with your end goal in
mind. Is it to just meet new people? Is
it just uh you're trying to sell
something? Is it that you are trying to
get feedback, expand your brand? And you
might think, I don't want to be sounding
selfish or too um into myself. That's
fine. you if you start with the end goal
in mind and reverse engineer it, it's
going to be more impactful for you as
well as the people that you're
networking with. There are so many bots,
there's so much technology, sometimes
you're not even talking to a human. Um,
I've seen so many interesting things
over the last couple weeks. um with AI
that you have to have your end goal in
mind and that way even if it is a human
or a technology and assistant the person
themselves you can benefit from that
conversation because you know what
you're trying to get out of it. So
another thing too is planning the
followup. So that's the the comp this is
like one a so one know what you want to
get out of the event and one a is plan
the followup before attending. What are
you going to follow up and say? Are you
going to send them a link? Are you going
to send them a resource? have it all in
one place cuz I know I know I am not the
best at followup. I
actually built a solution to help me
with followup and I'm we're going to be
dropping a YouTube video on the GSSE
solutions channel to talk about what the
solution is uh that is going to be
helping me with followup and leveraging
the networking. So I'll tease a little
bit of it towards the end of this
episode, but keep watching. Um and if
you're watching live, go ahead. If you
have any questions for me, go ahead and
put them into the chat while I talk to
you about three ways that you could use
AI in the well, three ways you could
leverage and maximize networking and
events in the age of AI. So number one
and one a is know what you want out of
the event and then plan the followup
before attending. So whether that's
resources, links, uh information that
you want to send, have it somewhere so
that way when it's time to follow up, it
makes it easier. I again, I used to suck
at followup. Um and so when I started
doing this, it helped tremendously
because I didn't have to go scatterbrain
and go all over the place to find
information. It was all in one space and
I could copy the links, send this text,
customize this piece, and it made it
easier to follow up and build that true
relationship because relationship
building is one of the skills that is
not going anywhere. It doesn't matter
how many AIs are in the middle. It's
humans at the two ends of that. And if
you don't know how to build a good
strong relationship, you're going to
lose out on clients, business partners,
friends, colleagues, life partners.
You're going to lose out in so many
different ways. when raising your kids,
you're going to lose. And I don't want
you to lose. I want you to win.
Especially as a leader and an operator.
You have too many things on your plate
right now to be not able to follow up
and follow through with the
communication. So that's one and one a.
Number two, make it easy to connect. I
cannot tell you how many times I've been
to networking events both in person and
virtual and someone is like, "Oh, you
know, tap my phone, share this link,
scan this QR code, and it brings me to a
page where I have to fill out
information or I have to click on 25
different links and I don't know, do you
want to connect on LinkedIn? Do you want
to connect on Instagram? Do I email you?
Do I do this? Do I do that?" And it just
starts spinning. All of this starts
spinning. And maybe their best
interactive platform for the other
person is LinkedIn. your best platform
is Instagram and you may have messaged
them on LinkedIn, but then you don't
check back in or you follow them on
Instagram instead of LinkedIn and now
they're not checking back in. It just
don't don't make it hard to interact
with that person. So, you have to make
it easy to connect with you and then
make it easy for them to connect with
you. I think I said the same thing
twice. What I'm trying to say, this is
real time, y'all. What I'm trying to say
is
whatever links you're sending to the
person or whatever you're trying to
share, make that easy for them to
receive. And then when you are
collecting their information, make it
easy for you to receive. So on both
sides, make it easy to receive. And stay
till the end. You're going to want to
stay to the end. I'm literally so
excited about this thing that I uh was
working on. Can't wait to tell y'all.
I'm trying to hold back because I'm like
I have other content that like I have a
whole
don't think I have more content to
share, but I'm literally just so excited
about it. [snorts] Um, and then number
three is followup. Followup eats me up
every single time. Who, if you're
watching right now live, like I'm
literally about to look at the comments.
Who here loves followup and followup is
just so easy for you to do because like
raise your hand. Let me know because I
be struggling. And if you have any tips
for me, let me know. But I think I built
something that is going to make my
followup chef's kiss so easy, so
seamless moving forward. Um, all right.
So, follow up. When I say followup, that
is making sure you message the person,
making sure you email them, making sure
you interact with them after that first
interaction. You met at a networking
event, virtual or in person, message
them back on LinkedIn, email them back.
And setting specific time on your
calendar to do that. That's again I am
not the follow-up queen but I want to be
one day and that was a tip that really
changed the game for me when it came to
followup. If I have again everything
planned out beforehand, I make it easy
to connect and then I actually do the
followup because I have my system right?
It's a follow-up communication
interaction networking system that I'm
building. It made it so much easier to
actually build strong healthy
connections with the people that I was
meeting at events. Right? So, I wanna
that's like the first bucket of stuff
that I want to talk about with the three
ways to maximize networking and events
in the age of AI. Now, the stuff that
I'm excited about.
So, I'm going to show y'all a few
things. So, let me get my screens um
going. And while I'm doing that, go
ahead and let me know in the comment
section again if you're watching this
live or you're watching the replay. How
do you balance and manage follow-up
interactions? How do you network in the
age of AI? Do you have your bot talk to
somebody else's bot? Like, how do you
actually benefit from networking, making
connections in the age of AI?
So, I got my screens. I'm excited. I'm
excited. All right. So, I'm going to
share my screen with y'all, and we're
going to go through some of the
different uh tools that I actually use
while networking and helping me to
maximize my networking in the age of AI.
All righty, let's get this going.
All right, I'm going to share a tab at a
time. The first tool that I want to talk
about is uh Luma. So, Luma, if you
aren't familiar, is this website that
has a bunch of different events and you
can discover events. And I would like to
say it's kind of like the 2026
Eventbrite. Eventbrite still does exist,
but I know when I first started
networking maybe 10 years ago, you know,
12 years ago, Eventbrite was the place
to find all the events. Um, no matter if
the event was hosted on another platform
and go to Eventbrite, then you end up on
Splash that you end up on this page that
page and it's a discovery platform and I
also used to use what is it called? Um,
Gary's Guideen NYC. So, it's a discovery
platform as well as a hosting uh
platform where you could put events up
if you have an upcoming event. So, I
really like that feature on um Luma. So,
here is my Luma and it's like, you know,
I'm interested in, you know, it asks you
what you're interested in. But I usually
go on a couple, you know, once maybe
twice a week to see what's coming up and
register for a few events. Um, Partle is
another platform. I That one is more so,
it has some tech and business events,
but that's more so like just community
networking events and things of that
nature. But definitely Luma is a
platform that's in my tech stack when
I'm thinking about networking,
especially in the age of AI. Another
platform that I used to use. Um, so
we're going to go to the past a little
bit, is called Lunch Club. So, I don't
know if they've changed or what's going
on over there. I recently signed up
again in the last like two months, but I
haven't gotten any conversations yet.
I'll still sh plug them because in the
past it was super helpful for me where
it matches you to um random people based
on like your interest, who you're trying
to get to know, what you're trying to
talk about. So, lunch club, you'll get a
couple minutes. Hopefully, y'all get it
together and start giving me some
meetings. The next tool, so I'm I'm
going up in level of excitement, right?
So, the next tool that I've been using a
whole whole lot in networking is called
Bordy. So, if you haven't heard of Bory,
it is simply an AI tool. It's super
conversational and it will allow you to
get introduced to different people. So,
Bour connects you with people in its
network. So, think of it as like almost
like a it's going to sound terrible,
like a p I don't want to say a person.
Think of it like LinkedIn. Like if
LinkedIn all lived in like one AI and
then it's like oh I think you should
meet this person that person and it'll
tell you about their background and um
what they do and why you should connect
with them and different things of that
nature. So the way this works for
literally this is exactly it. I'll get a
text message um from board and they'll
like hey so and so is in this market
this is what they do. Would you be open
to an introduction? I told them this
about you and it's super conversational.
We go back and forth and then it
introduces me to the person that is best
fit. Um, so I'm I'm proud to say that
I'm maybe I'm at least 10 of these uh
20,995
introductions. That number was crazy to
say.
I struggled a little bit just just now.
But nonetheless, let's keep going. So
Bour is really does what it says it does
and it can connect to your calendar. I
personally don't have it connected to my
calendar because I have a thousand
different calendars that I kind of move
through. So, it'll suggest some times
from the other people's calendar and
then I will pick one of those times. And
I also don't want it to just be sending
out all the times because sometimes I'm
like fake available, not available. Does
anybody do you do that too? Right?
You're available but you block the
calendar for a work session and so
you're technically not available in that
time. Um, so Bour definitely recommend
as a tool for networking. I've met so
many cool people on there. I've been
featured on a podcast because of it. Um
I'm I'm having maybe like two to four
conversations a week through board
introductions. So if you think about how
you would normally get introduced to a
person one-on-one, like let's say you
have a mutual colleague or a mutual
friend, Bour is doing that at like super
speed. Um and I think there's a little
bit less of a friction because it's um
it's warm, right? It's a warm connection
because it's like we're all in the
boarding network, but you know that it's
like an intelligent tool. So, it's like
really scanning to see if this is a good
fit for an introduction for you. Um, so
I do appreciate that piece, that element
of Bordy. Um,
so let's keep going.
All righty. Where are we? All right.
Now, the big one. This is what I was
saying to watch till the end. So, if
you've made it, we're here. Come on.
Come here. Come here. Come here. Lock
in. Lock in. I have a whole YouTube
video about this, but I wanted to share
with you all. I use uh Meta's app. Meta
Meta's tool, Muse. Is it app tool?
Whatever. Muse by Meta. And to build out
a like, it'll scan the business card.
And I'm pretty sure half of y'all going
to be real excited about this and half
of y'all going like, "Girl, didn't you
know you could do that from before? I
didn't know." So I hope the half that is
discovering this for the first time like
I did is having a great time. So Muse is
new. So on Muse, what I was able to do,
oh, let's go back. So Muse is from Meta.
It's their new AI personal assistant,
and it's giving very much Jarvis vibes,
like really strong quality a AI
assistant. I've used a few before, but I
think this one takes the cake and like
actually getting the thing done. And I'm
all things GSD, get it done. So, I
reached out and I was like, "Hey, I need
a way for you to scan the business cards
and get the person's information, draft
a follow-up email." Because what happens
is that I go to these events, and I've
been doing this for years. I'd go to the
event and I would get a stack of
business cards and I would manually back
in the the heyday I would manually enter
in these business cards into
um a spreadsheet that I had. So I'd
manually enter the business cards into
the spreadsheet. After I put them into
the spreadsheet, then I would go through
and manually email each person and
follow up directly. So that was method
number one. Phase two, I then started
using mailmerge and I would add custom
notes. So that way it's, you know, still
me, but the mail merge would send all
the emails at once. Instead of me taking
30, 40 minutes, an hour, it would be
like five minutes. I just got to enter
them. Mail merge emails. Then I wanted
to kind of remove myself from the first
part. So I started having a VA. I would
take a picture, scan the business cards,
send them to the VA, they would enter it
into the spreadsheet, then I would come
in, you know, uh, and do the the mail
merge and get the the the last mile. And
I was like, what if I could just have
the business cards be as soon as I take
the picture, it's inside of the sheet
and take it a step above, right? I could
also have the follow-up drafted and all
I have to do is review the follow-up
email and just say send and approve and
that's it. It's done. And I could make
follow-up easy, right? Because that was
was creating a gap for me in networking
and maximizing my interactions and
events. I I was tired of this like pile
stacking up and you'd forget and you
have different things to do and I had to
catch up back with work all the things
that were happening and so now enters
Muse and me and my team we've been
talking about um using uh building out a
solution where I would text the an AI
the card kind of what I just mentioned
to solve for that and I got a response
from Claude and it just seems so
cumbersome. I again I'm going to link
the video down below so I don't take too
much time to talk about it and it just
was so much it just seemed like so much
work for me to get from like where I'm
at right now with the prompt to like
actually finishing this thing. So I was
like let me throw it into Muse. So I
connected my calendar and uh no my email
and a spreadsheet. It did its thing. Set
it up. Then I was like let's test it
out. So I had some business cards. So I
sent it the business cards and it was
four cards on uh no I sent four
different images. Four different images.
And in the future I'm actually going to
test it out. Can I send like a picture
of like 10 business cards at once? Can
that work? It puts it in a spreadsheet
and then it drafts up emails.
Literally,
this is what I've been talking about.
It's now a reality.
And so when I think of networking and
maximizing my time in the age of AI, you
know, between boardy making
introductions for me, between Luma
finding different events and maybe I
could have my AI scan Luma and say like
what are the best events that I should
attend this week based on what I'm
trying to accomplish as goals. I'm
pretty sure somebody up there has that
workflow and I'm going to implement it
to myself because we only have so much
time. AI is not going anywhere. It's
moving faster than us. But I do
prioritize the humanto human connection.
I want to get to the point where we are
in the meeting. We are, you know, or in
the work session. We're at the event. We
are in the interaction. And a lot of the
the miscellaneous stuff kind of in
between
don't need to be on my task list, right?
I want to make do meaningful work, high
quality strategic builder work and
coordinating and putting emails into a
spreadsheet may not be the best use of
my time. And so I hope this episode of
Ora lunch and learn has been helpful for
you to think about how you are
networking and maximizing your time
through using AI. I shared a few tools
today. They're going to be linked below.
I've shared some apps and platforms and
I also shared some strategies in the
beginning and networking events are not
going anywhere but we could use the AI
tools at our disposal to increase our
own productivity. That's really the goal
and productivity for positive output and
outcomes not not to just like be in a
loop because that's a next that's
another conversation for another time.
And so I think what I've shared here
shows you how you can leverage these
tools, still keep the human aspect and
focus on maximizing when I am in person
and connecting and not panicking. Oh,
I'm going to forget to send you a
follow-up email. Let me start drafting
that while we're still middle of the
conversation. I could focus on creating
or bond having an actual conversation
with the people or people's or people or
persons that I'm talking to. Person or
people that I'm talking to. English is a
hell of a language. uh [laughter]
the people that I'm talking to and then
afterwards the followup be handled and
then I could get back into more
conversations, more interactions with
those people, that person. Yeah. So, I
hope you enjoyed this lunch and learn
and you learned something. If you have
any questions, go ahead and leave them
down below in the comment section. If
you want to watch the videos that I
mentioned around um the elaboration of
how we got to build out or muse solution
and kind of what I was trying to build
in Claude before and just kind of like
the thinking and the prompts and the
methodologies, definitely go ahead and
watch that video. Uh make sure you like
this video if it was helpful. Subscribe
to our channel and we will see you in uh
a future lunch and learn. But please,
you know, keep engaging. We're here with
these lunch and learns every single
week. If you don't get to watch the
live, go ahead and watch the replay when
you can. And I don't see any questions
in the chat at this time. So, I'm going
to head off. I hope you enjoyed this and
I'll see you soon.
Thank you so much for tuning in to
today's lunch and learn session. These
are weekly sessions brought to you by
GSSE solutions where we unpack AI
systems, operations, and all the fields
that are connected to them. So, make
sure you tune in to next week's session.
If you want to watch the replay, you can
watch them both on YouTube and on
LinkedIn. Also, be sure to subscribe to
our newsletter. We can't wait to see you
in another lunch and learn session.
Thanks so much for watching. Have a good
one.